<lesson>
    <title>Welcome to Tiny Teach</title>  <!-- Title of lesson : REQUIRED -->
    <audio>./lesson1/lesson1.mp3</audio>  <!-- Location of audio file : REQUIRED -->
    <slide>
        <in>0.0</in>  <!-- When this slide begins in seconds : REQUIRED for slide -->
        <out>30.0</out>  <!-- When this slide ends in seconds : REQUIRED for slide  -->
        <notes><![CDATA[<b>Welcome to Tiny Teach</b><br/><br/>
        Tiny Teach is a NOOC (<i>Normal Open Online Course</i>).  Similar to a MOOC (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Massive_open_online_course" target="_blank">Massive Open Online Course</a>), Tiny Teach is a simplified bare-bones web application that adds annotations and slides to audio recordings listed in a dynamic directory.  This application allows for the rapid development and deployment of medium sized (1-1000 seat) classroom lessons.]]></notes>
        <image>./lesson1/image1.jpg</image> <!-- Image for current slide -->
    </slide>
    <slide>
        <in>30.0</in>
        <out>66.0</out>
        <notes><![CDATA[<b>The goal of Tiny Teach</b> is to take audio recordings and add timed multimedia features via HTML in a structured and coherent fashion.  Tiny Teach uses the Popcorn.js library to sync slide events to audio.  XML is used to structure the slides for publication on the platform.<br/><br/>
        Lessons are read directly from the lesson directory, creating a dynamic list of available courses. <u>Tiny Teach is also responsive</u>, making it ideal for students who only have access to mobile technologies.]]> </notes>
        <question>What type of rich, engaging lessons would you create?</question>  <!-- Question for current slide -->
        <image>./lesson1/image2.jpg</image>
    </slide>
    <slide>
        <in>66.0</in>
        <out>90.0</out>
        <notes>It is hoped that in this manner, any educator can create short high-quality lessons (10-15 minutes) within 60-90 minutes.  These NOOCs become tiny reinforcements of classroom content or a powerful series of additional curriculum enhancements.  Enjoy Tiny Teach.  Use it to engage, upgrade and empower your classroom! </notes>
        <image>./lesson1/image3.jpg</image>
    </slide>
</lesson>
